SOUTH KOREA CRUSADE WITH T.B. JOSHUA
Prayer Time
Rise up, rise up for prayer.
South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
With this mass prayer, you can be reached!
If there is any area of your life you need prayer for and you have challenges,
I know you will recover after this mass prayer.
Mass Prayer At The South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
You will recover, in the name of Jesus!
Jesus will touch you, right now!
I command that spirit that torments your life, in the name of Jesus -
that familiar spirit - out!
Out!
Mass Prayer At The South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
I command you to leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
You evil spirit, I command you to leave my people, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Say out!
Out!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Open your lips and begin to rebuke that spirit that torments your life!
In the name of Jesus, begin to rebuke that spirit!
Cast out the spirit! Cast it out!
You evil spirit!
Mass Prayer At The South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Begin to cast them out!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Mass Prayer At The South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Every spirit of sickness, disease, infirmity, affliction - begin to cast them out!
I rebuke you - leave my people!
Open your lips - begin to cast out this spirit!
Mass Prayer At The South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Open your lips and begin to cast out the spirit -
the spirit that torments your life!
That spirit of sickness in your blood!
That spirit of sickness in your bones - right now, cast them out!
Mass Prayer At The South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Bring them out!
Mass Prayer At The South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Bring them out!
I rebuke you, in the name of Jesus! I say, come out - you evil spirit!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Because she can save many souls, I cannot let her live!
Mass Prayer At The South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
I stopped her from evangelising. I made her a fool
because she will save many souls.
All powers of demons, familiar spirits - I say, out!
You power of demon, you familiar spirit - come out!
I say, out!
Out!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
You don't care.
Mass Prayer At The South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
I destroyed her life.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
All power, all demon power,
familiar spirits, power that kills, steals and destroys - I command you out!
I say, out!
I say, out, in the name of Jesus!
Mass Prayer At The South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I'm going to kill her! I'm going to destroy her!
I will not tell you! I will kill her!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I will kill her!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Whatever you might have eaten in the dream,
whatever you might have eaten from the table of demons,
right now, begin to vomit them out!
By the blood of Jesus, vomit them!
Right now, out of your blood!
Begin to vomit them out, by the blood of Jesus and the power of the Holy Ghost!
Holy Ghost!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I will kill her!
I'm going to kill her.
Why did she come here?
I will kill her and I will also kill her child.
I will also kill the child.
I gave her the child and I made the child disabled.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Right now, begin to separate yourself! Separate yourself from familiar spirits!
Every power that is not of God -
begin to separate yourself, in the blood of Jesus and the power of the Holy Ghost!
Holy Ghost!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I'm not going! I will never leave her!
Holy Ghost!
In the name of Jesus!
Right now, every pain, every sickness, every disease!
Those of you on the wheelchair, right now, begin to exercise your freedom!
Rise and walk!
In the name of Jesus!
Wherever the sickness or disease - in your bones - out!
In your kidney - out!
I say, walk!
Walk!
Mass Prayer At The South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Right now, those of you on the wheelchair, begin to walk!
Right now, give thanks to God!
Hallelujah! Give thanks to God!
If you are just coming to Christ or you are here to rededicate yourself,
right now, open your lips and say after me, "Lord Jesus, come into my heart,
wash me with Your precious blood, save my soul today!
You are my Lord, my Saviour, my Redeemer, My Deliverer, My Healer!
Thank You, Jesus. In Jesus Christ's name!"
Hallelujah!
Mass Prayer At The South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
For You save me how can I be still
I will sing for joy to the Lord
For You forgive my sin how can I be still
I will worship for joy to the Lord
My love for You my heart for You
Can't stop loving You
I will dance for joy
For He turns my sorrow into praises
My whole life is in Your hands Oh Lord
South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
Because You saved me I cannot be still
I will sing for joy to the Lord
Because You forgave my sin I cannot be still
I will worship the Lord with joy
My love for You my heart for You
Can't stop loving You
I will dance for joy
For He turns my sorrow into praises
My whole life is in Your hands Oh Lord
South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2
I will dance for joy
I will shout to the Lord
I will jump to the Lord
I will shout louder
My love for You my heart for You
Can't stop loving You
I will dance for joy
For He turns my sorrow into praises
My whole life is in Your hands Oh Lord
No more shackles
No more chains
No more bondage
I am free
No more shackles
No more bondage
No more chains
I am free
No more shackles
No more chains
No more bondage
I am free
Hallelujah
South Korea Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 2